《阿凡达》电影的续集为什么要拍4部啊
Why are they making four more Avatar movies?
第一部都没多好看
It's not like the first one is even that good.
听你在胡扯  你明明超爱那部电影
What are you talking about? You love that movie.
那年万圣节你还打扮成阿凡达了
You even went as Avatar for Halloween.
历历在目啊  那衣不蔽体的画面
I remember. That was not a lot of clothes.
你们来啦
Hey, guys.
我...  我今天店里有特殊活动
I'm, uh, I'm running a special today, uh,
买任何产品  能获得这漫画店不倒闭
buy something, keep having a comic book store to come to.
这就尴尬了
This is awkward.
我本来打算来退这本漫画呢
I was actually gonna return this.
这漫画哪里出问题了
What's wrong with it?
我看完了
I-I finished it.
说到我觉得有趣的事
Speaking of something I find interesting,
你们读了我发的比特币的文章了吗
did anyone read that article about Bitcoin I sent you?
有啊  我真没想到一个比特币
Yeah, I can't believe a single Bitcoin
现在能值五千块美金
is worth about $5,000 now.
等等  我们好几年前不是挖过比特币吗
Wait, didn't we mine some a few years ago?
是七年前
It was seven years ago.
对啊  我记得了
Oh, yeah, I remember that.
真的吗  我唯一记得起的七年前事物
Really? All I can remember from seven years ago
是当时我脑海中不停播放凯沙的歌"滴答"
is I couldn't get Kesha's "Tik Tok" out of my head.
♪ 滴答  时间不停走 ♪  欢迎回家  凯沙妹子
? Tik Tok, on the clock... ? Whoa, welcome home, Kesha.
我们绝对挖了一些币
No, we-we definitely mined some.
我还记得坐在你房间然后写了程序
I-I remember sitting in your bedroom and writing the program.
我们当时好像还挖出了不少呢
I think we ended up with a bunch of it.
现在一个币值五千  那...
Wow, and at, like, $5,000 apiece, that's...
那听起来是一笔巨款啊  当时我们说好平分
Sounds like a lot of money, which we agreed to share
因为当时我绝对在场  我刚想起来
'cause I-I was totally there. I remember now.
真不敢相信我们忘了这事
I can't believe we forgot about it.
这也不奇怪
It's not that surprising.
我们拿到手的时候根本不值钱
They were basically worthless when we got them.
真想知道我们有多少币
I wish I knew how much we had.
谢尔顿你肯定记得
Sheldon, you must remember.
当然啦
Of course I do.
对啊  我跟他绝对都记得
Oh, yeah, he and I totally remember.
你跟大家说吧  谢尔顿
You tell them, Sheldon.
7年前
真不敢相信你还没去看《阿凡达》
I can't believe you haven't seen Avatar yet.
你有毛病啊
What is wrong with you?
我跟佩妮刚开始交往
Penny and I just started dating,
你也知道我不喜欢人太多的地方
and you know I don't like big crowds.
因为你怕佩妮会跟人群中的某人跑了吗
Because you're afraid Penny will leave you for someone in them?
怕死了
Terrified.
所以他们不像常人出去约会
Yes, instead of going out,
而是待在房里不停交媾
they just stay home and have constant coitus.
我不想说出来  但听到这话还挺爽
Well, I didn't want to say it, but I-I do like to hear it.
会啦  妈  我会回家吃饭
Yes, Ma, I'll be home for dinner.
我才不会吃糖果吃到晚饭吃不下
No, I'm not ruining my appetite with candy.
今晚有炖牛胸吗
Oh, we're having brisket?
我6点准时到家
Be home at 6:00.
或许我们可以四人约会
Maybe we should double date.
我带佩妮  你带老母
I'll bring Penny and you can bring your mom.
随你吐槽
Oh, make your jokes,
但我的伴帮我开了储蓄账户
but my date started a savings account for me.
你的伴有吗
Did yours?
-大家好啊  -好啊
- Hey, you guys. - Hey.
斯图尔特  太好了  我正想问你
Oh, Stuart, good. I was wondering,
你这里收比特币吗
will you be accepting Bitcoin?
我不知道那是什么  但它带有一个"币"字
Well, I don't know what that is, but it's got "coin" in it,
而我的收银机里没有币  我收
and my cash register doesn't, so... yeah.
等等  什么是比特币
Wait, what's Bitcoin?
是一种新开发出来的线上货币
It's a new online currency that's been developed.
跟真的钱没啥两样
Uh, it's just like actual money,
只不过你看不到  摸不到  买不了任何东西
except you can't see it, hold it, or spend it on anything.
感觉是我很熟悉的一种钱
Sounds like the kind of money I'm familiar with.
如果不是有形的货币  你怎么能确定
If it's not tangible, how do you know
它不会一夕之间就消失了呢
it's not just gonna vanish tomorrow?
不是吧  你在跟佩妮交往  而你居然还想多问
Really? You're dating Penny, and you're gonna poke at something
明天就可能消失的事物吗
that could vanish tomorrow?
我愿意买点比特币
I'll buy some Bitcoin.
我最近刚到手一小笔钱
I just came into a little extra money
我爸给我涨了零花钱
when my dad raised my allowance.
比特币不用买
You don't have to buy Bitcoin.
你可以自己挖出来
You can mine it.
挖  就像挖金子吗
Mine it? Like, mining gold?
类似吧  比特币的总数是有限的
Sort of. There's a limited amount,
我们想获得  不是往地心挖坑
and we find it, not by tunneling into the earth,
而是用电脑运算复杂的数学问题来获得
but by using a computer to solve complex mathematical problems.
让我理理
So let me get this straight.
所以我们得精心写个程序
We have to write an elaborate program
来挖出我们花不了的假货币吗
in order to find a fake coin that we can't spend on anything?
-是的  -听起来真"有趣"啊
- Yes. - ?That sounds fun.
我加入
Yeah, I'm in.
一起熬夜  写代码  感觉像个派对啊
Staying up late, writing code, it sounds like a party.
斯图尔特
Hey, Stuart.
你想跟我们一起挖比特币吗
You want to mine some Bitcoin with us?
我们写程序  你带零食
We'll write the program, you bring the snacks?
太高档  穷人玩不起
Too rich for my blood.
好吧  那就我们四个人挖
All right, so just the four of us.
开挖前先说好
Before we begin,
这可能会造成史无前例的税务问题
this may have some unprecedented tax implications.
其实我们最好快点开始
In fact, we should start early 'cause
到时候国税局可能会打电话跟我们谈很久呢
we are gonna be on the phone with the IRS for hours.
有人也兴奋到起鸡皮疙瘩了吗
Did anybody else just get goose bumps?
很好  就我们三个挖吧
Great, so just the three of us.
想起来了  我们没带你
Oh, yeah. We did it without you.
今时今日
你还记得后来发生什么事了吗
And do you remember what happened next?
你妈打给我妈说我们欺负你
Your mom called my mom and said we were being mean?
在那之后呢
And after that?
你说有一天我们会后悔
You said that someday we'd regret this.
那你知道今天是什么日子吗
And do you know what today is?
我们发现自己发财了而你屁都没的日子吗
The day we found out we're rich and none of it is yours?
对啊  击个掌
Yeah, that's right! Up top!
第十一季  第九集
今时今日
这是我2010年时用的笔记本电脑
Okay, this is the laptop i was using in 2010.
比特币肯定就在这里面
The Bitcoin must be on here.
你拿到钱之后打算怎么处理
So what are you gonna do with your share of the money?
身为一个有责任心的大人
Uh, well, as a responsible adult,
我会把钱拿去做定存  等定存到期了
I'll put that money into a CD, wait for that CD to mature,
就拿去买只老虎
and then buy a tiger.
那你呢
How about you?
得看我告不告诉伯纳黛特了
Oh, that depends on whether I tell Bernadette or not.
霍华德  我能听见你说话  宝宝监控器开着呢
Howard, I can hear you. The baby monitor is on.
我知道  我说笑呢  我会为孩子存起来
I know. I was joking. I'm gonna put it in a college fund.
好啦  开好机啦
All right, all booted up.
我知道你当年是单身狗
Wow, I-I knew you were single back then,
但这也太多黄片了吧
but that is a lot of porn...
科学  是好多科学
Science! A lot of science.
那你非常喜欢"亚洲的科学"啊
Wow, you were really into Asian science.
电脑里没看到比特币啊
I don't see the Bitcoin on here.
或许是在那个叫
Hey, maybe it's in that folder marked
"私人机密档案"资料夹里
"Private and Confidential."
不在那里面
It's not!
7年前
准备好执行挖矿程序了
Okay, the program is almost ready to run.
挖金币听起来好爷们啊
Mining for coins sounds so manly.
或许我们该唱首挖矿歌
Ooh, we should sing a mining song.
你会任何挖矿歌吗
Do you know a mining song?
不知道
I don't know.
凯沙的"滴答"算吗
Does "Tik Tok" by Kesha count?
这首歌挖洞钻进了我的心房
Because it has tunneled its way into my heart.
霍华德  你们在干嘛呢
Howard, what's going on?!
你们在大乱斗吗
Are you boys roughhousing?!
不  我们没在大乱斗
No, we're not roughhousing!
我们是科学家  科学家不会大乱斗
We're scientists! Scientists don't roughhouse!
抱歉打扰了  大人先生
Excuse me, Mr. Grown-up.
怎么回事
Aw, man, what happened?
死机了
It crashed.
最近常常这样
It's been doing that lately.
应该是中毒了  因为我...
I think it's got a virus from all the...
下载了很多"音乐"
music I've been downloading.
什么类型的音乐
What kind of music?
大部分是亚洲的
Mostly Asian.
还有些老的
Some oldies.
可以用我的电脑
Well, we can use my laptop.
霍华德  我给你和小伙伴们做了曲奇
Howard, I made cookies for you and your little friends!
他们不是我的小伙伴  我们也不要吃曲奇
They're not my little friends, and we don't want cookies!
其实我还挺想吃曲奇的
Actually, a cookie sounds good.
好吧  我们要吃曲奇
All right, we'll have cookies!
谢谢你了
Thank you very much!
今时今日
对了  肯定是在我的旧电脑里
That's right. It must be on my old laptop.
快走吧
Well, let's go.
妮妮  我能不能去一下莱纳德家
Hey, Bernie, you mind if I run to Leonard's and...
取一台装满钱的电脑吗
Get a laptop full of money?
还傻坐着干什么  快去啊
Why are you still here?! Go, go, go!
婚礼计划得怎么样啦
So, how's the wedding planning going?
很好
Great.
不过举办地点我俩还没商量好
Although, we're having trouble agreeing on a location.
你们之前不是在找海滩边上的悬崖吗
I thought you were looking at a cliff on the beach.
是啦  但谢尔顿一个都不喜欢
We were, but Sheldon didn't like any of them.
有些太海滩  有些太悬崖
Some were too beachy, some were too cliffy.
而且所有地点都太室外了
And all of them were too outsidey.
婚礼的重点不在于地点
Well, weddings aren't about the location.
最重要的是站在你们亲友面前
They're about standing up in front of your family and friends
发誓谢尔顿永远不会搬回这里
and promising that Sheldon will never move back in here.
好啊
Hi.
你们几个干嘛呢
What are you guys doing?
我们有台旧电脑里有些比特币
Uh, we have a bunch of Bitcoin on an old laptop,
也许能值很多钱
and it could be worth, like, a lot of money.
什么  你逗我呢吧
What-- You're kidding.
没有  我们可能坐在金山上
No. We-we could be sitting on a fortune.
我要先声明  我当初嫁给你不是为了钱
Okay, let the record show, I did not marry you for money,
但你忽然变得有魅力多了
but you just got way more attractive.
我靠  不在这里面
Damn it, it's not in here.
要是你们当时有个过目不忘的朋友在场就好了
If only you had someone around with an eidetic memory.
我猜他肯定记得电脑哪去了
I bet they would know what happened to it.
你如果知道  就快告诉我们
If you know, just tell us.
不好意思  但如果我没记错七年前的事
Excuse me, but if I recall from seven years ago,
你们不想要我参与这件事
you don't want me to be a part of this.
谢尔顿  你不会还在生气吧
Sheldon, you can't still be mad.
拜托
Oh, please.
我幼儿园时期的仇都还记着呢
I have grudges that go back to preschool.
总有一天  我要找到长大的伊莱恩·德怀尔
Someday, I'm gonna find a grown-up Elaine Dwyer
在她面前吃掉她最爱的蜡笔
and eat her favorite crayon while she watches.
所以我们宴请名单上才有个伊莱恩·德怀特吗
Is that why there's an Elaine Dwyer on our guest list?
没错
Yes.
到那晚  我便能拥有第一支舞
That night, I'm going to have the first dance
和最后胜利者的一笑
and the last laugh.
谢尔顿  拜托了
Sheldon, please.
我该大人有大量吗
Should I be the bigger man?
我觉得应该
I think you should.
我脑子抽了才会问你
Oh, why'd I ask you?
7年前
好啊  美人
Hey there, pretty lady.
我不会帮你服务你的客人
I'm not waiting on your table for you.
拜托啦  这个客人真的很讨厌
Come on, this one is so annoying.
不好意思  服务员
Excuse me, waitress.
二位要点餐了吗
You guys ready to order?
能帮我们拍张照吗
Can you take our picture, please?
没问题
Oh, sure.
笑一下
Smile!
完美
Perfect.
谢谢  你可以退下了
Thank you. You may go now.
很高兴认识你
It was nice to meet you,
我这是客套话  不是真心的
and I mean that politely, not sincerely.
刚刚是怎么回事
What was that?
我需要证明给我妈看  我正在约会
I need to prove to my mother that I'm on a date.
如果她觉得照片是我伪造的
If she thinks I faked the picture,
我可能需要你当人证  你叫什么名字
I might need you as a witness. What's your name?
伯纳黛特
Bernadette.
亲爱的
Hey, sweetie.
都吃得开心吗
Everybody good?
嗯
Yeah.
-挺好  -开心
?- Fine. ?- Sure.
你不用说悄悄话  点个头就行了
You don't have to whisper, you can just nod your head.
或者直接说也行
Or you could just speak.
你今天顺利吗
You having a good day?
不好  我错过了试镜
No, I missed an audition
因为我电脑坏了  没收到通知邮件
because my computer broke, and I didn't get the e-mail.
本来是个超适合我的角色
Would've been a perfect part for me.
是演一个无视客人的服务员吗
Was it waitress who ignores her customers?
你天生就是演这个的料
Because that's the role you were born to play.
闭嘴吃你的汉堡
Shut up and eat your burger.
其实是火鸡三明治
Actually, it's a turkey club.
你点的不是汉堡吗
Didn't you order a burger?
是的  但你不从人愿
I did, and yet here we are.
你如果要用电脑
You know what, if you need a computer,
可以用我的
you can use my laptop.
你真贴心  但我不会要你的电脑
Oh, that's sweet, but I'm not gonna take your computer.
没事  反正我也要买新的了
Oh, it's fine. I-I'm getting a new one anyway.
-你确定吗  -别傻了
- Are you sure? - Don't be silly.
他拼了命想抓紧你
He's desperate to hold on to you.
你想从他那拿走什么都行
You can get anything out of him.
他的车  他的表
His car, his watch...
拿个肾估计也没问题  你已经得到他的蛋蛋了
Maybe a kidney. You already have his testicles.
可以集齐一整套
You can start a collection.
今时今日
天啊  是这样没错  你把电脑给我了
Oh, my God, that's right. You gave me your laptop.
你太好了
That was so sweet.
-这么说你知道在哪了  -当然啦
- So you know where it is? - Of course.
-好耶  -棒  -太好了
- All right! - Yes! - ?Great!
我给我前男友扎克了
I gave it to my ex-boyfriend Zack.
-不是吧  -不要啊
- Come on! - ?No!
今时今日
好的  扎克  谢谢你
Okay, Zack, thank you so much.
我们这就过去
We'll be right over.
电脑还在他那
He still has it.
真不敢相信你把我送你的礼物
I can't believe you took a gift from me
转送给其他男人了
and gave it to another man.
不是吧
Really?
她给其他男人送过那么多"甜头"
Of all the things she's given to other men,
你却只在意这个吗
that's what you're concerned about?
不要小题大做了
Please don't make a big deal about this.
那是很久之前的事了  我们当时分手了
It was a long time ago, we were broken up.
是哪一次分手
Which breakup was that?
是"情人节大屠杀"吗
Was that the Saint Valentine's Day Massacre?
不  不是
No, no.
可能是"漫展大怒甩"期间
This might've been during the Comic-Con Dump-A-Thon.
你们还给我们每次分手取名了吗
You have names for our breakups?
如果不这样  可能会分不清
Well, they would really blur together if we didn't.
漫展那次分手很容易记住
The Comic-Con breakup's easy to remember
因为莱纳德扮的是最难过的皮卡丘
because Leonard was the saddest Pikachu.
没错  然后他用你的披风擤鼻涕
Right, and he wiped his nose on your cape,
你就变成最悲催的黑武士了
and then you were the saddest Darth Vader.
话说  不是只有我和佩妮分过手
You know, Penny and I aren't the only ones who've broken up.
霍华德和伯纳黛特也分过
So did Howard and Bernadette.
不是要炫耀啦  但我每次分手都一分到底了
Uh, not to brag, but all my breakups have lasted.
7年前
你和霍华德分手了  我很遗憾
I'm so sorry to hear about you and Howard.
谢了  我真是看不出来
Thanks. I just didn't think he was
他是那种在网上乱来的人
the kind of guy who would be doing weird stuff online.
真的吗  我觉得特别明显呀  不过行吧
Really? Wow, I thought it was so obvious, but okay.
我知道分手很难熬  但我觉得
Look, I know it's hard, but I think the best thing
分手后最该做的就是沉淀一下
to do after a breakup is to take some time
好好享受单身时光
and be by yourself.
这才是健康的
Yeah, that's healthy.
宝贝儿  可以走了吗
Hey, babe, ready to go?
学我所言  而非我行
Do as I say, not as I do.
今时今日
我真不敢相信你会生气
I cannot believe you're mad.
我没有生气
I'm not mad.
真的吗  对你的眉毛说去
Oh, really? Tell that to your eyebrows.
我在中间放一个硬币
Bet I could place a quarter between them,
都能停得稳稳当当
and it would just stay there.
好吧  我生气了
Fine, I'm mad.
我只是觉得我比你对分手更感到难过
I guess I was more upset by our breakup than you.
才怪  我当然也很难过
That is not true. Of course I was upset.
看起来不像呀
Didn't seem like it.
你立刻就跟你找到的第一个
You started dating the first
又高又帅的肌肉男搞上了
tall, handsome hunk you could find.
不好意思
I'm sorry,
你是气我上了他  还是气自己没上到他
are you mad that I dated Zack or that you didn't?
-嗨  -你好扎克
- Hi. - Hey, Zack.
真高兴见到你们
So good to see you guys.
我们应该多几次这样的相聚
Man, we should do this more often.
不停地回来找你要笔记本电脑吗
Come over to get laptops back from you?
对啊
Totally.
你还留着那电脑吗
So do you have it?
当然啦  那是佩妮送给我的礼物
Of course I do. Penny gave it to me as a gift.
这么重要的礼物怎么能乱丢呢
You don't get rid of something like that.
抱歉我把你那台蠢电脑送掉了
All right, I'm sorry I gave away your stupid laptop.
你道歉是应该的  我们当时才刚分手
You should be. We were broken up for, like, five minutes.
你俩在吵架吗
Are you guys fighting?
-对  -没有
- Yeah. ?- No.
你们在为是否在吵架这件事而吵吗
Are you fighting about whether or not you're fighting?
我也跟人吵过这个架
'Cause I've had that fight before.
最后发现我们真的在吵架  而我输了
Turns out we were, and I lost.
莱纳德觉得我和他分手时一点都不难过
Leonard thinks when we broke up, it didn't bother me.
怎么可能
That's crazy.
我和她交往时  她不停地在说你的事
When we were going out, she used to talk about you all the time.
老实说  我觉得她和我约会
In fact, I think she only dated me
仅仅是因为我让她想起了你
because I reminded her of you.
好吧
Sure.
因为咱俩都...
Because we're both...
是人吗
people?
说对啦
Damn right we are.
对了  里面还有一段讲述她如何思念你的视频
Oh, also, there was that video about how much she missed you.
-什么视频  -电脑上的那个
- What video? ?- The one on the laptop.
我没想窥探你的隐私  但我就是爱管闲事
I didn't mean to invade your privacy, but I am a huge snoop.
不信问我的邻居  她会告诉你
Ask my neighbor. She'll tell you.
但别现在去问  她正在洗澡呢
But not right now; she's in the shower.
7年前
你好  莱纳德
Hello, Leonard.
我本打算给你写封邮件  但是我喝得有点高
I was gonna write you an e-mail, but I'm a little drunk,
而拼写这件事适合清醒的人去做  所以...
and spelling is a sober person's game, so...
我感觉我欠你一个"姐释"
I feel I owe you a 'splanation.
对不起
I-- I'm sorry.
一个"姐释"
A 'splanation.
佩妮  佩妮
Penny. Penny.
佩妮
Penny.
谢尔顿  走开  我在拍影片呢
Sheldon, go away. I'm making a video.
抱歉  等你一个人  方便的时候我再过来
Oh, I'm sorry. I'll come back when you're alone.
不  不是的  我一个人在家
No, no, no. I am alone.
我在向莱纳德解释我为什么和他分手
I'm just telling Leonard why I broke up with him.
他清楚得很
Oh, he knows.
我倒是想看看
The video I want to see
解释你为什么和他交往的视频
is why you went out with him in the first place.
我和他交往是因为他这人很棒
I went out with him because he's great.
如果我们继续这样下去
And if I kept going out with him,
我大概就会和他结婚了
I probably would've married him,
这让我有点害怕
and that's a little scary
因为我还没有做好结婚的准备
because I just don't think I'm ready for that.
再说  我真得学学如何拼写霍夫斯塔特
You know, plus I have got to learn how to spell Hofstadter.
我知道里面有"塔"字
I-I know there's a "D" in there,
但每次一写  它就跳来跳去
but it keeps moving every time I try and write it.
谢尔顿  我该怎么做
Sheldon, what do I do?
昏睡过去时记得面朝下  以免被呕吐物呛死
Try to pass out facedown, so you don't choke on your vomit.
我才不会昏睡过去
I am not gonna pass out.
但还是要谢谢你
But thank you anyway.
-哇  -对啊
- Wow. ?- I know.
她后面还这么趴了两个多小时
There's, like, two more hours of her just lying there.
原来你这么爱我
Aw, you love me so much.
我都和你结婚了好吗  猪头
I married you, jackass.
我知道  而且不是因为同情我
I... I know, and not just out of pity
大家的婚礼祝福都说错了
like everyone said in their wedding toast.
你们想看她最后摔下椅子的画面吗
You want to see the part where she falls off the chair?
-不想  -想看
- No. ?- Totally.
这才是我老婆
That's my wife.
我要再看一遍
I got to see that again.
-拿到电脑了  -快拿过来
- Got the laptop. - Hand it here.
我的小心脏好紧张
Oh, this is so exciting!
等我们卖掉比特币  你会把这些年来
Hey, when we sell the Bitcoin, are you gonna pay your dad back
剥削你爹的钱财都还给他吗
all the money you took from him over the years?
想都没想过
Never even crossed my mind.
找到比特币文件夹了
Okay, here's the Bitcoin folder.
里面有多少钱
Yeah, how much is in there?
里面是空的
It's empty.
什么  怎么可能
What? Th-That's impossible.
难道是扎克偷了吗
Do you think Zack stole it?
他才不懂怎么偷比特币
No, he doesn't know how to steal Bitcoin.
他还会跟路上的卡车司机打招呼呢
I mean, he waves at trucks.
那会是谁干的呢
Hmm... who could it have been?
谢尔顿  你做了什么
Sheldon, what did you do?
我策划了我的报仇大计
I plotted my revenge.
如果你有盘子  我就为你呈上一盘复仇
If you get a dish, I'll serve you some cold.
你偷了我们的比特币吗
What, y-you stole our Bitcoin?
冷静
Oh, calm down.
我只是偷偷登录了你的电脑
All I did was sneak onto your computer
把你们的比特币下载到U盘上了
and download your Bitcoin onto a flash drive.
什么
What?
我没有占为己有
I'm not keeping it.
我只是想看你着急到满头大汗
I just wanted to watch you sweat.
你要想看他出汗
If you want to watch him sweat,
只需要和他爬一层楼梯就行了
walk up a flight of stairs with him.
我等待了7年之久  终于等到了
I've waited seven long years, but it finally happened.
我们的钱在哪里
Where's our money?
这才是最妙的部分
That's the best part.
其实就在你钥匙串上的蝙蝠侠U盘里
It's on the Batman flash drive on your key chain.
一直都在你的口袋里呢
You've had it in your pocket all along.
谢尔顿
Sheldon...
我的钥匙串早就丢了
I lost that key chain years ago.
真的吗
Really?
你  你  有没有到处找找吗
D-D-Did you look under things?
真是太不幸了
Well, that is unfortunate.
我想我们今天都学到了一课
I guess we've all learned a lesson today.
我们学到了什么呀
What was the lesson?
我也不知道
I don't know.
4年前
那是什么
Huh. What's that?
蝙蝠侠的U盘呢
Ooh, Batman flash drive.
真不错
Pretty cool.
如果我把它格式化
Huh, if I erase this,
还可以卖个10块钱呢
I could probably resell it for, like, ten bucks.
小康生活在向我招手啦
Things are finally going my way.